Mr. President, we're trying to get your selection for the NATO summit.
Yep, I think this looks, uh, this looks just fine.
What's this?
This the layout for NATO?
Turin?
This is what we're gonna wear in Turin.
This is it?
This is it.
Can I make a suggestion?
Speak your mind.
Bring some extra ties.
Why do we need extra ties?
I guess they tend to stain.
I don't stain my ties.
You know why my ties are immaculate?
No.
Why?
I never eat soup or pasta when I'm wearing a tie.
You have to make a choice.
You get soup or tie, not both.
Is that so?
Yeah, I noticed you eat soup, that's why your ties are all messed up.
Think about it.
Interesting.
What about the flip up?
Flip up doesn't work.
You know why?
What flips up, flops down.
Might make it worse, you might end up with your tie in the soup.
Ruins both the tie and the soup.
I get it.
Quite an expert on this.
Here's a schedule for Turin.
All right, what do we got here?
Let's see.
What's this?
It's a drink.
What kind of drink?
It's a protein smoothie.
Oh, really?
What's it called?
I'm not sure, I'm not sure what it's called.
You're not sure?
Yeah.
Doesn't have a name?
Mango tango.
You're drinking a mango tango.
That's nice.
You don't have to yell.
Can I have a little taste?
No, man, you can't have a sip of my drink.
It's a big deal.
I mean, it's not a big deal, it's just not something I'd prefer.
You're using the straw.
I would just be sipping from the glass.
Well, that'd be worse.
How's it worse?
You're putting your mouth on the surface of the glass.
Your saliva would get in the drink.
So you're a no-sips guy?
No, no, I give sips.
Michelle can always have a sip.
If Malia and Sasha were here, I would gladly give them a sip.
Uh-huh.
But not you.
What about Panetta?
No, not Panetta.
Biden?
No.
I think you have to have boundaries.
So no non-family sips?
Nope.
Also, you, Biden, Panetta, old lips.
Old lips.
Yeah, it's not appetizing.
By the way, old lips, I love that as a nickname.
Okay, old lips, let's get back to the schedule.
Okay, let's do it.
This looks pretty good.
Good.
I do wish we had more time in the Alps.
A lot of stuff we could be doing.
People can go skiing, take some hikes.
Really?
You ski?
Why would you assume I don't ski?
Do you ski?
Yeah.
All right, so you think you can ski and I might not be able to ski?
I will, well, no.
What would lead you to assume that I don't ski?
Oh.
Larry, is it because...
No, no, no, no.
Is it because...
No, no, sorry, Bob.
Is it because I'm from Hawaii?
Obviously, yes.
Hawaiian ski, too, Larry.
Hawaiian ski?
Yeah.
Ah, who knew?
I knew.
Oh.
Wondering if you could do me a little favor when you're over in Turkey.
At the NATO summit, you want me to do you a favor?
Tiny little thing.
It's nothing.
What is it?
Tell the Danish prime minister that I said hello.
That's all.
In the middle of the NATO summit, when we're discussing critical national security issues, you want me to say to her, hey, you know what?
Larry said hi.
That's all you got to do.
What do you think is going to happen?
Just wondering what her reaction might be.
You know what I think her reaction would be?
I think she'd say, Larry, who?
I don't think so.
You didn't observe our conversation two years ago when we were there.
You think it was as memorable to her as it was to you?
I made her laugh.
Oh, you're so funny.
That's how she said it.
That's how she said it, yeah.
She said, oh.
Oh, you're so funny.
You're funny.
Larry.
Yeah.
I am not going to do that.
Are you insane?
Why?
She's the Danish prime minister.
She doesn't know who you are.
I made a big impression on her.
She knows who I am.
Not to mention the whole tell somebody I said hi thing.
Nothing happens out of that.
Let's play this out.
I'm in the NATO summit.
You want me to go up to the Danish prime minister in the middle of this thing and say, oh, lips, Larry says hi.
Then I come back.
I have to then tell you, Hella says hi.
Now what?
Nothing happens.
Now, I bore in on the attitude.
You bore in?
Yeah.
What does that mean?
That means, how did she react?
Did she go?
Ooh, ooh, Larry said hi.
You tell Larry I said hi too.
Larry, that's not a discussion I want to have.
All right?
Let's just get back to work.
Sure.
All right.
What's that about?
It's classified.
I'm not going to tell you.
Why?
I'm tremendous at keeping secrets.
You know, my cousin Arthur was a bigamist.
He had a wife in New Hampshire, one in Queens.
He'd go back and forth every other weekend.
He didn't tell anybody.
I'm the only person he told, and I never told a soul.
You told me.
He's dead.
Yeah.
Okay.
And I've confided a lot of sensitive stuff with you.
I told you about the time I pooped in my pants when I was 12 years old on the bus going to the town of the gardens.
Where you started telling me this, didn't want to hear it then, don't want to hear it now.
You can imagine how it traumatized me.
I don't really want to imagine it.
12-year-old boy, there were girls on the bus, and they called me Diaper David for years.
That's confidential information.
There's a reason why you didn't get classified clearance.
Your behavior confirms that was a wise decision.
Is it Russia?
China?
Nope.
Taiwan.
Oh, my God.
Taiwan?
Excuse me, Mr. President.
We have the press conference on ISIS in 10 minutes.
Okay.
Got it.
All right.
I've got to check on a couple things.
I'll be right back.
Sure.
Yeah.
Take your time.
Oh, all
right.
I think I'm ready to go.
Hey!
You know what?
I got an idea that just might interest you.
What's your idea?
I think you should wear the tan suit to the press conference.
For this press conference?
Yes.
Why?
Well, first of all, it's a gorgeous suit.
And that's why I'm taking it to Turin.
There's a daytime event.
It's outdoors.
A little more casual.
And this is Casual Friday.
Hey, Brian, the boss wants to try on the tan suit.
I do love this suit.
It's perfect.
You're casual.
And it's in the briefing room.
It's not in the East Room.
Where's your time?
Having lunch and, uh, gonna get some soup.
I'm gonna get some soup.
You're taking my advice?
Yeah, smart, huh?
Yeah.
One last tip, though.
A little bit of a rookie mistake.
When you take the tie off, you gotta pop the top.
Oh, I'll pop the top.
Yeah, it'll look cooler.
Yeah, thank you.
Oh, oh, it is a great suit.
Oh, boy.
I think this is the move.
I'm gonna try it out, see how it looks.
Old lips won't let you down.
You'll thank me.
What do you think?
Pretty good.
Pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty good.
All right, let's go.
I got a press conference to do.
You sure about this?
Never been more sure about anything in my life.
Okay.
I'll be back.
People are going to be talking about this for a long, long time.